[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island in the Pacific Ocean is surrounded by a lagoon and a barrier reef.", "correct_answer": "Bora Bora", "incorrect_answers": ["Cyprus", "Thasos", "Tupai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which feature on the surface of Mars inspired Iron Maidens song Face in The Sand, included in their album Dance Of Death?", "correct_answer": "The Face on Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["The Skull on Mars", "The Martian Belt", "The Red Eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is Tom Hankss character, Sam Baldwin, a lonely father in the 1993 romantic comedy Sleepless in Seattle?", "correct_answer": "He is a widower.", "incorrect_answers": ["His wife left him because he cheated on her.", "He never had a wife, he adopted his son.", "He asked his wife for some time out."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wolves do not wag their tails as dogs do when they are happy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This zodiac sign is ruled by Mercury. People born under it often change their mind.  They are also known as being tender and caring.", "correct_answer": "Gemini", "incorrect_answers": ["Leo", "Libra", "Aquarius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oklahoma has no cities and communities named after Presidents.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In his twelve-volume analysis, this British historian wrote that history was not a continuous climb upward, but a series of  waves or pulses, where civilizations rise, prosper and eventually fall.", "correct_answer": "Arnold J. Toynbee", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Beard", "Howard Zinn", "Frederick J. Turner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these marine mammals matches the description: Very large body, has tusks and whiskers?", "correct_answer": "Walrus", "incorrect_answers": ["Tusked seal", "Elephant seal", "Polar bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what century was the word pink used for the first time?", "correct_answer": "17th century", "incorrect_answers": ["18th century", "16th century", "19th century"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the German doll that inspired Ruth Handler to create the popular fashion doll Barbie?", "correct_answer": "Bild Lilli", "incorrect_answers": ["Francie", "Breeana", "Midge Hadley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This health care discipline uses mostly the technique of spinal adjustment.", "correct_answer": "Chiropractic", "incorrect_answers": ["Rolfing", "Acupuncture", "Alexander Technique"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which member of the Wayans family starred in the 1996 movie Bulletproof with Adam Sandler?", "correct_answer": "Damon", "incorrect_answers": ["Shawn", "Kim", "Nadia"]}]